{
    "subject": "resource/Saudi_Press_Agency",
    "predicate": "ontology/headquarter",
    "object": "resource/Riyadh",
    "human_readable": "The headquarters of Saudi Press Agency are located in Riyadh.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9883217215538025,
            "question": "Is Saudi Press Agency headquartered in Riyadh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9690952897071838,
            "question": "Where are the headquarters of Saudi Press Agency located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.946818470954895,
            "question": "In which country is Saudi Press Agency headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9422377347946167,
            "question": "Name the city that houses the headquarters of Saudi Press Agency."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9269147515296936,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Saudi Press Agency's headquarters are situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8270084261894226,
            "question": "Where is the main office of Saudi Press Agency located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7964972853660583,
            "question": "If you wanted to visit the headquarters of Saudi Press Agency, which city would you go to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7056928873062134,
            "question": "What city serves as the operational base for Saudi Press Agency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6534008979797363,
            "question": "What is the location of Saudi Press Agency's central offices?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5785336494445801,
            "question": "Saudi Press Agency's main operations are centered in what city?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The headquarters of Saudi Press Agency are located in Riyadh.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3733_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the location of Saudi Press Agency's central offices?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3733_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city serves as the operational base for Saudi Press Agency?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3733_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you wanted to visit the headquarters of Saudi Press Agency, which city would you go to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3733_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3733_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3733_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3733_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3733_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3733_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3733_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3733_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3733_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3733_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3733_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as it is stated that \"The agency is headquartered in the capital, Riyadh\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3733/re-ranker-msmarco/66.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis response is based on the information provided in the document with the file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3733/re-ranker-msmarco/66.txt`, which explicitly states, \"The Saudi Press Agency (SPA) is headquartered in the capital, Riyadh.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}